One town. One night. Ten chilling stories.
Tales of Halloween is a horror, thriller, adventure
film directed by Darren Lynn Bousman.
Ten stories from horror's top directors.
Ghosts, ghouls, monsters, and the devil delight in terrorizing unsuspecting
residents of a suburban neighborhood on Halloween night.
This creepy anthology combines classic Halloween
tales with the stuff of nightmares.
The Stranger, played by Keir Gilchrist.
Bobbie, played by Pollyanna McIntosh.
Hank, played by Sam Witwer.
Isaac, played by Booboo Stewart.
The Radio DJ, played by Adrienne Barbeau.
Alice, played by Gracie Gillam.
Tales of Halloween is a 2015 American comedy horror anthology film consisting
of ten interlocking segments, each revolving around Halloween.
Segments were directed by Neil Marshall, Darren Lynn Bousman, Axelle Carolyn, Lucky McKee, Andrew Kasch, Paul
Solet, John Skipp, Adam Gierasch, Jace Anderson, Mike Mendez, Ryan Schifrin, and Dave Parker.
The film premiered on July 24, 2015, at the Fantasia International Film Festival, before receiving a
limited theatrical release and through video on demand on October 16, 2015, by Epic Pictures.
The film explores themes of witch, based on novel or
book, halloween, anthology, death.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.